Tufts Journal UP054
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Journal
1980 -- 2006
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Communications
UP054
2.65 Linear Feet
10 Volumes
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of the Tufts Journal beginning in 1980 published by the Office of Communications. It is a newspaper devoted to news about Tufts and Tufts staff members. It is "distributed free to members of the Tufts community." Distribution is monthly online, but only September-December and February-May in paper format. Beginning with the September 2001 issue the Tufts Journal became an online only publication. Begining November 2003, a paper version began publication again. After May 2006 the Tufts Journal became an online only publication. Missing: Vol. 19 #7 (April 1998).
- Tufts Journal, 1980 -- 2006; UP054.001; 2.65 Linear Feet; 10 Volumes
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of The Tufts Journal. It is a monthly newspaper produced by the office of communications. It is "distributed free to members of the Tufts community" and devoted to news about Tufts and Tufts staff members. It began publication in 1980. Beginning with the September 2001 issue the Tufts Journal became an online only publication. In November 2003, it returned to paper format with distribution from September-December and February-May. It continues to be published monthly in an online format.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Tufts Journal, January 31, 1980; UP054.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Journal, February 14, 1980; UP054.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Journal, February 28, 1980; UP054.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Journal, March 13, 1980; UP054.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    A-21 Task Force deals with federal funding regulations. p.1, 6
  - Tufts Journal, March 27, 1980; UP054.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    Administration 1980. Acting Associate Provost.
  - Tufts Journal, April 10, 1980; UP054.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Journal, April 24, 1980; UP054.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    Status report of [A-21 Task Force] p.6
  - Tufts Journal, May 8, 1980; UP054.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
    [Admission, Office of, 1980] Freshman applications increase 2%. Nadya Aisenberg (Faculty). Recieves NEH stipend.
  - Tufts Journal, May 22, 1980; UP054.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
    Academic Awards 1980, seventy-two receive awards; [Alumni] photo essay on alumni art; [Alumni council] Honors outstanding graduates
  - Tufts Journal, June 18, 1980; UP054.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
    Administration 1980. Michael A. Hoffman named executive vice-president (includes photo).
  - Tufts Journal, July 16, 1980; UP054.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Journal, September 4, 1980; UP054.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
    Administration 1980-81. Senior administrators promoted.
  - Tufts Journal, September 18, 1980; UP054.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
    [Accreditation] Effort for 1980 begins. pp. 1, 8
  - Tufts Journal, October 2, 1980; UP054.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Journal, October 16, 1980; UP054.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
    [A-21 Task Force] Survey of library users. p. 2
  - Tufts Journal, October 30, 1980; UP054.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
    [Admissions, Office of, 1980-81] [Alumni 1980-81] Volunteers aid Admissions Office (includes photo), p. 2, 8.
  - Tufts Journal, November 13, 1980; UP054.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
    [Administration] Trustees name provost, three vice presidents, pp. 1, 3.
  - Tufts Journal, December 4, 1980; UP054.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Journal, December 18, 1980; UP054.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Journal, January 14, 1981; UP054.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Journal, January 29, 1981; UP054.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
    Acton Project offers opportunities for teamwork, service. p. 5
  - Tufts Journal, February 12, 1981; UP054.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
    [alumni council] Continuing education program offers wide range of courses
  - Tufts Journal, February 26, 1981; UP054.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Journal, March 12, 1981; UP054.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
    [Administration] Federal court dismisses Carton's suit, p. 2.
  - Tufts Journal, April 2, 1981; UP054.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Journal, April 23, 1981; UP054.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
    [Alcohol Abuse 1981] Programs on alcohol.
  - Tufts Journal, May 28, 1981; UP054.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
    Amelia Peabody Day at Veterinary school [includes photo]; [Alumni association] Seniors honored for achievements, Academic awards for Academic Awards 1981. Academic awards to 75 students, one professor.; [Administration] Provost, executive Vice President approval expected. pp. 1, 7; [Afro-American Cultural Center] Presents seventeen awards, p. 6. [Alumni 1981] Varied events set for alumni weekend, p. 1, 5.
  - Tufts Journal, June 17, 1981; UP054.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Journal, July 15, 1981; UP054.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
    [Alumni association] Professor Alice Palubinskas recieves Distinguished Service Award; [Alumni association] Marvin M. Pollack recieves distinguished service award; [Administration] New administrators in place. (photos). p. 1.; Sol Gittleman appointed new Provost; Steven Manos appointed new executive Vice President. p. 1.
  - Tufts Journal, August 19, 1981; UP054.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
    [Administration] Drive and humor mark Mano's approach, p. 1-2.
  - Tufts Journal, September 2, 1981; UP054.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Journal, September 17, 1981; UP054.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
    [Administration] Carton, Lonnie. Court allows Carton dismissal. p. 2.
  - Tufts Journal, October 1, 1981; UP054.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Journal, October 15, 1981; UP054.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Journal, October 29, 1981; UP054.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Journal, November 12, 1981; UP054.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Journal, December 3, 1981; UP054.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
    [Accreditation, Veterinary School] Vet school gets provisional accreditation p. 1; [Administration] Three administrators promoted (Kathryn Dowd, Audrey Hale, Carla Ricci). p. 3.
  - Tufts Journal, December 17, 1981; UP054.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
    Profile of Bertha Allen of Morning Musicales (BSOT) (photo).
  - Tufts Journal, January 14, 1982; UP054.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
    Mastrovita, Robert P. and Stepanian, Ira named Alumni Trustees, p. 2.
  - Tufts Journal, January 28, 1982; UP054.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
    [Afro-American Cultural Center] Nikki Giovanni opens Black History Month (photo), p. 3.
  - Tufts Journal, February 11, 1982; UP054.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Journal, February 25, 1982; UP054.001.003.00012 (Box 3)
    [Alumni council] Continuing education program courses set
  - Tufts Journal, March 11, 1982; UP054.001.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Journal, March 25, 1982; UP054.001.003.00014 (Box 3)
    [Accreditation] NEASC names team for reaccreditation study. pp. 1, 6; [Alumnae] Presidents ball in Wessell library
  - Tufts Journal, April 15, 1982; UP054.001.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Journal, April 29, 1982; UP054.001.003.00016 (Box 3)
    [Admissions] Record number of early decisions. p. 1.
  - Tufts Journal, May 13, 1982; UP054.001.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Journal, May 27, 1982; UP054.001.003.00018 (Box 3)
    Alumni council honors 12 seniors; 2500 alumni expected on campus
  - Tufts Journal, June 15, 1982; UP054.001.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Journal, July 14, 1982; UP054.001.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Journal, August 11, 1982; UP054.001.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Journal, September 2, 1982; UP054.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Journal, September 16, 1982; UP054.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
    [Alumni 1982] First reunion for European alumni/ae at Talloires, p. 1.
  - Tufts Journal, September 30, 1982; UP054.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Journal, October 14, 1982; UP054.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Journal, October 28, 1982; UP054.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Journal, November 10, 1982; UP054.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
    [Africa and the New World] New minor in African culture (photo), p. 4; [American association for Accreditation of Laboratory Animal Care] Health sciences center accreditation approved
  - Tufts Journal, December 2, 1982; UP054.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Journal, December 16, 1982; UP054.001.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Journal, January 13, 1983; UP054.001.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Journal, January 27, 1983; UP054.001.004.00010 (Box 4)
    [Afro-American Cultural Center] Tufts celebrates Black history month, p. 3.
  - Tufts Journal, February 10, 1983; UP054.001.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Journal, February 24, 1983; UP054.001.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Journal, March 10, 1983; UP054.001.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Journal, March 24, 1983; UP054.001.004.00014 (Box 4)
    Continuing education committee of alumni council announces schedule
  - Tufts Journal, April 7, 1983; UP054.001.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Journal, April 21, 1983; UP054.001.004.00016 (Box 4)
    [Alumni association] Tufts service citations presented to Alla Korjagin; [Admissions] Freshmen applications increase. pp. 1, 3. [Akiba, Tad] (Faculty) To be one of the rotating guest editorial column writers for the Japanese newspaper "Mainchi Shimbun" magazine "The Economist".
  - Tufts Journal, May 5, 1983; UP054.001.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Journal, May 19, 1983; UP054.001.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Journal, May 26, 1983; UP054.001.004.00019 (Box 4)
    [Alumni 1983] Italian Fiesta, Boston Pops alumni weekend events, p. 1; [Alumni association] Former provost Shira, Ullman recieve Distinguished Service Awards
  - Tufts Journal, June 15, 1983; UP054.001.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Journal, July 14, 1983; UP054.001.004.00021 (Box 4)
    [Alumni 1983] Nickless, Fred named acting director of alumni relations, p. 4; [Alumni relations] Fred Nickless named acting director of alumni relations
  - Tufts Journal, August 17, 1983; UP054.001.004.00022 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Journal, August 31, 1983; UP054.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Journal, September 15, 1983; UP054.001.005.00002 (Box 5)
    [Alumni council] Continuing education fall series
  - Tufts Journal, September 29, 1983; UP054.001.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Journal, October 13, 1983; UP054.001.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Journal, October 27, 1983; UP054.001.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Journal, November 10, 1983; UP054.001.005.00006 (Box 5)
    [Alumni 1983-84] Brinn, Ronald C., new director of alumni relations, p. 1-2; Ronald Brinn new director of alumni relations [includes photo]
  - Tufts Journal, December 1, 1983; UP054.001.005.00007 (Box 5)
    [Aesthetic Decisions] Decisions by artists, critics, p. 5.
  - Tufts Journal, December 15, 1983; UP054.001.005.00008 (Box 5)
    [Accreditation, Veterinary School] Vet school given full accreditation p. 1.; [Administration] Durgin, William, Vice President for finance resigns (photo). pp. 1-2.
  - Tufts Journal, January 19, 1984; UP054.001.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Journal, February 2, 1984; UP054.001.005.00010 (Box 5)
    [Administration] General counsel position created; Mary Lee Jacobs named (photo). p. 1. [Alexander, David] "Children's Computer Drawings": article accepted for publication by Instructor magazine.
  - Tufts Journal, February 16, 1984; UP054.001.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Journal, March 1, 1984; UP054.001.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Journal, March 15, 1984; UP054.001.005.00013 (Box 5)
    [Alumni council] Continuing education program for 1984; [Admissions, Office of, 1984] Applications increase. Ainsworth, Keith (a 1987). Hopes to carry Olympic Torch (photo). [Alumni 1984] Continuing ed. program for 1984, p. 5, 8.
  - Tufts Journal, March 29, 1984; UP054.001.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Journal, April 12, 1984; UP054.001.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Journal, April 26, 1984; UP054.001.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Journal, May 17, 1984; UP054.001.005.00017 (Box 5)
    [Alumni weekend] Highlights of 1984 alumni weekend; [Adopt-a-Grandparent] Feature article with photo. p. 7. Tad Akiba (faculty) Appointed senior fellow of the Nikkei Industry Research Institute of Japan. Frank Allen (F84) Fletcher graduate wins federal internship. [Alumni 1984] Alumni Association awards presented for following: Distinguished Service Awards (5), Tufts Service Citations (4), Seniors Awards (12), p. 15. [Alumni 1984] Distinquished Service Awards given to six, p. 2.
  - Tufts Journal, June 13, 1984; UP054.001.005.00018 (Box 5)
    [Adulyadej, Bhumibol (King of Thailand)] Mayer to present honorary degree to King of Thailand. p. 1. Thomas Allen (G 85) Awarded a French teaching assistantship.
  - Tufts Journal, July 18, 1984; UP054.001.005.00019 (Box 5)
    [Administration] New Dean of Administration: Lawrence Ladd. p. 2.
  - Tufts Journal, August 15, 1984; UP054.001.005.00020 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Journal, August 30, 1984; UP054.001.006.00001 (Box 6)
    [Alumni council] Continuing education program offered; [Administration] New Dean of Administration: Lawrence Ladd. p. 5.; [Adulyadej, Bhumibol (King of Thailand)] Mayer to present honorary degree to King of Thailand. p. 5. [Alumni 1984-85] Continuing Education Program offered, p. 5.
  - Tufts Journal, September 13, 1984; UP054.001.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Tufts Journal, September 27, 1984; UP054.001.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - Tufts Journal, October 11, 1984; UP054.001.006.00004 (Box 6)
    Alonso, Juan M. Published Articles in the Christian Science Monitor, pg. 8 [Alumni 1984] Homecoming draws alums, p. 1,7.
  - Tufts Journal, October 25, 1984; UP054.001.006.00005 (Box 6)
    [Alumni 1984-85] New alumni relations team announced, p. 2, 5; New alumni relations team announced
  - Tufts Journal, November 8, 1984; UP054.001.006.00006 (Box 6)
    [Afro-American Cultural Center] Braithwaite, Marilyn A. has been appointed as assistant director of the African American Center, p. 7. [Akiba, Tad (faculty)] Participant in two international symposia. David Albertini (Faculty) Speaker at symposium in Atlanta by the American Society of Cytology later this month (November).
  - Tufts Journal, November 29, 1984; UP054.001.006.00007 (Box 6)
    [Alumni council] Sponsors east Africa tour; [Agency for International Development] Awarded grant of $300,000 to assistant professor Beatrice Rogers for food pricing study, p. 6.
  - Tufts Journal, December 13, 1984; UP054.001.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - Tufts Journal, January 17, 1985; UP054.001.006.00009 (Box 6)
    [Administration] Academic Audits [1985; 1986]. Departments undergo academic audit.
  - Tufts Journal, January 31, 1985; UP054.001.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - Tufts Journal, February 14, 1985; UP054.001.006.00011 (Box 6)
    [Alumni 1984-85] New alumni-student links, p. 2.
  - Tufts Journal, February 28, 1985; UP054.001.006.00012 (Box 6)
    [Alumnae] President's Ball; [Alumni/ae] Eliot-Pearson alumni host seminar day
  - Tufts Journal, March 14, 1985; UP054.001.006.00013 (Box 6)
    [Alumni council] Continuing education program set; First alumni college to be held; Tadatoshi Akiba (faculty) Associated with two books in Japanese: "The Computers with Faces" and "Three Levels of Time" (photo).
  - Tufts Journal, March 28, 1985; UP054.001.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - Tufts Journal, April 11, 1985; UP054.001.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - Tufts Journal, April 25, 1985; UP054.001.006.00016 (Box 6)
    Mayer addresses alumni council; [Alumni/ae] Jumbo club honors five alumni
  - Tufts Journal, May 16, 1985; UP054.001.006.00017 (Box 6)
    [Alumni/ae] Jumbo weekend in 1985; [Alumni association] Names officers; [Admissions, Office of, 1985] Business as usual under the elms; [Alumni association] Honors six for service to Tufts: Richard W. Ballow, Linda Dixon [J1963], Elias Dow [M1953], Janet (Getchell) Manzelli [J1950], Robert Meehan [A1955], Thomas Swift [A1959][D1963]
  - Tufts Journal, June 12, 1985; UP054.001.006.00018 (Box 6)
    [Administration] Trustees approve administrative changes. pp. 1-2.
  - Tufts Journal, August 14, 1985; UP054.001.006.00019 (Box 6)
  - Tufts Journal, September 5, 1985; UP054.001.006.00020 (Box 6)
    [Phillip G. Allston] Fletcher appoints two new faculty members; Accreditation committee to visit dental school. p. 2 Pamela Allara (administration) Named associate dean of the Museum School program.
  - Tufts Journal, September 19, 1985; UP054.001.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - Tufts Journal, October 3, 1985; UP054.001.007.00001 (Box 7)
    [Alumni/ae] Sponsor fall program
  - Tufts Journal, October 17, 1985; UP054.001.007.00002 (Box 7)
    Tadatoshi Akiba (faculty, math) Represented the Norbert Wiener Forum of Tufts at joint meeting of forum in Tokyo, Japan.
  - Tufts Journal, October 31, 1985; UP054.001.007.00003 (Box 7)
    [Phillip G. Allston] Lectured on "The Future of the United Nations' at Harvard Law School; ASEAN [Association of Southeast Asian Nations] conference to address Singapore p. 7
  - Tufts Journal, November 14, 1985; UP054.001.007.00004 (Box 7)
    Tadatoshi Akiba (faculty) Guest panelists at "Unforgettable Fire" symposium sponsered by Mass. College of Art.
  - Tufts Journal, December 5, 1985; UP054.001.007.00005 (Box 7)
    [Alumni/ae] Tufts club of Boston debuts [includes photos]; David Alexander (E-P Dept. Child Study Admin.) Presented paper titled "Children's Computer Drawings: Are they Developmental? Is it Art?". Juan Alonso (faculty) Presented paper on "The Modern Novel's Voice", p. 4.
  - Tufts Journal, December 19, 1985; UP054.001.007.00006 (Box 7)
    [American association of University professors] TIAA/CREF decides against divestment
  - Tufts Journal, January 16, 1986; UP054.001.007.00007 (Box 7)
    [Accounting Procedures Manual] Sponsored Programs Accounting offers accounting tips. p. 7. David Albertini (Faculty) Presented research seminar at Mayo Clinic Foundation in Rochester, Minn.
  - Tufts Journal, January 30, 1986; UP054.001.007.00008 (Box 7)
    [Philip Alston] Spoke on human rights trials in Argentina at Harvard lecture
  - Tufts Journal, February 20, 1986; UP054.001.007.00009 (Box 7)
    [Alumni relations] New associate director joins alumni staff; Tadatoshi Akiba (faculty) Keynote speaker at the First Mainchi Women's Seminar in Tokyo. [Alumni 1986] Alumni relations names new associate director (Eileen Schell), p. 2.
  - Tufts Journal, March 6, 1986; UP054.001.007.00010 (Box 7)
    Dental School wins accreditation. pp. 1, 3.; [Admissions, Office of] Tufts appoints new dean of admissions, David Cuttino. p. 1.
  - Tufts Journal, April 3, 1986; UP054.001.007.00011 (Box 7)
    [Alumni council] Continuing education announces courses; [Aga Khan, Sadruddin] Recipient of honorary doctor of humane letters degree, p. 1. [Alumni 1986] Continuing Education announces courses, p. 3.
  - Tufts Journal, April 17, 1986; UP054.001.007.00012 (Box 7)
  - Tufts Journal, May 1, 1986; UP054.001.007.00013 (Box 7)
    Kathleen Akins Presented paper at a conference on the relevance of neuroscience to philosophy. David Alexander (faculty) Parents learn from children.
  - Tufts Journal, May 15, 1986; UP054.001.007.00014 (Box 7)
    [Alumni association] Tufts service citation recipients: Linda Dixon [J1963], Ronald J. Milauskas [E1962][G1966], Katherine W. Baker, Theoharis Theoharides; [Alumni association] Senior awards recipients: Rachel S. Beuvoir, Kevin J. Cloherty, Gregory C. Davis, Barry G. Edelstein, Lisa B. Fair, Cheryl A. Hayes, Kevin M. Johnson, Paul C. Mitiguy, Micheal N. Obadia, Elizabeth Rabuczewski, Beth Rosen, Susan F. Sirota; [Alumni association] Distinguised service awards recipients: Bernard Berman [A1945][M1948], Lois (Leiper) DiLorenzo [J1943], Elizabeth (Van H0uysen) Mayer (wife of president); Norton Nickerson (faculty), Barry J. Rosenbaum [A1960]; Academic Awards 1986. Phi Beta Kappa inductees; [Aga Khan, Sadruddin] Recipient of honorary doctor of humane letters degree, p. 4; Addresses Fletcher School at commencement, p. 4. David Albertini (Faculty) Awarded grant with Eric Overstrom from USDA to study cellular differentiation during development of the porcine blastocyst.
  - Tufts Journal, June 19, 1986; UP054.001.007.00015 (Box 7)
    Tad Akiba [Faculty]. "Let's recognize teaching". David Albertini (Faculty) Co-recipient of grant of $115,109 with Eric Overstrom.
  - Tufts Journal, July 17, 1986; UP054.001.007.00016 (Box 7)
    [Phillip Alston] Elected as independent expert member of new United Natiuons Committee on Economic Social and Cultural Rights
  - Tufts Journal, August 27, 1986; UP054.001.007.00017 (Box 7)
    [American council of learned societies] Sponsored ninth USSR/US symposium on economics, held at Tufts June 1986
  - Tufts Journal, September 1986 -- August 1987; UP054.000274; 1 Volumes (Volume 12)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Transferred by Barbara Lewis, Administrative Coordinator for Communications and Marketing, 2022, accession UA-2023-026.
  - Tufts Journal, October 9, 1986; UP054.001.008.00001 (Box 8)
  - Tufts Journal, October 23, 1986; UP054.001.008.00002 (Box 8)
    [Alumni 1986] Sandra Ciolfi named alumni secretary, p. 6.
  - Tufts Journal, December 4, 1986; UP054.001.008.00003 (Box 8)
  - Tufts Journal, 1987 January 29; UP054.000272 (Box 8)
    Volume, Number
    8, 10
  - Tufts Journal, April 23, 1987; UP054.001.008.00004 (Box 8)
    [Alumni 1987] Civil Engineering alums gather for annual dinner, p. 2. [Alumni 1987] TUSVM (Tufts University School of Veterinary Medicine) alums celebrate homecoming, p. 4.
  - Tufts Journal, May 14, 1987; UP054.001.008.00005 (Box 8)
    [American academy of arts and sciences] Daniel C. Dennet elected to A&S academy; Alumni association honors nine; Alumni association salutes 11 outstanding seniors with senior awards
  - Tufts Journal, June 18, 1987; UP054.001.008.00006 (Box 8)
  - Tufts Journal, July 16, 1987; UP054.001.008.00007 (Box 8)
  - Tufts Journal, August 27, 1987; UP054.001.008.00008 (Box 8)
  - Tufts Journal, September 10, 1987; UP054.001.008.00009 (Box 8)
    [AIDS] Blanket AIDS testing has serious pitfalls. p. 3. Bruce Allen (faculty) Co-recipient, with Lawrence H. Ford, of $46,000 grant from the National Science Foundation.
  - Tufts Journal, September 24, 1987; UP054.001.008.00010 (Box 8)
    Adelphi University 1987-88. Tufts, Adelphi University, forge cooperative agreement; [Phillip Alston] Keynote speaker at Oxford University conference
  - Tufts Journal, October 8, 1987; UP054.001.008.00011 (Box 8)
  - Tufts Journal, November 5, 1987; UP054.001.008.00012 (Box 8)
    [AIDS] Blanket AIDS testing has serious pitfalls. (secrets) pp. 1-2
  - Tufts Journal, November 19, 1987; UP054.001.008.00013 (Box 8)
    [AIDS] Blanket AIDS testing has serious pitfalls. pp. 1-2; [Philip Alston] U.S. support of international agencies wanes
  - Tufts Journal, December 3, 1987; UP054.001.008.00014 (Box 8)
  - Tufts Journal, December 17, 1987; UP054.001.008.00015 (Box 8)
  - Tufts Journal, January 21, 1988; UP054.001.008.00016 (Box 8)
  - Tufts Journal, February 4, 1988; UP054.001.008.00017 (Box 8)
    Beth Adelson (faculty). Awarded $30,000 from National Science Foundation. Shrley Aidekman. Named vice chairwoman of Tufts' new capital campaign.
  - Tufts Journal, February 18, 1988; UP054.001.008.00018 (Box 8)
    [Phillip Alston] Politcal agendas threaten human rights
  - Tufts Journal, April, 1988; UP054.001.008.00019 (Box 8)
  - Tufts Journal, May, 1988; UP054.001.008.00020 (Box 8)
    [Amelia Peabody Foundation] Donates $1M, Tufts: the New Campaign
  - Tufts Journal, September, 1988; UP054.001.008.00021 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Amelia Peabody Foundation] Endowed professorship at vet school; [Phillip Alston] delivered paper in Stockholm; [Administration] Former Western Jr. High renovated to become Tufts Administration building (TAB), p. 4.
  - Tufts Journal, October, 1988; UP054.001.008.00022 (Box 8)